thebehemoth.com 2018-10-10

# The Behemoth - We Make Games

PRIVACY POLICY  
EFFECTIVE DATE: May 22nd 2018

The Behemoth ('The Behemoth,' 'we' or 'us') values the privacy of its online visitors, and hopes that the following statement helps you understand how The Behemoth collects, uses, discloses and safeguards the personal information you provide us through our web site, [www.TheBehemoth.com](https://www.thebehemoth.com/), and its pages (the 'Site'), as well as games, including online features of games, and any authorized mobile app operated by or at the direction of The Behemoth that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the 'Service'). 

**_Information The Behemoth Collects:_**

When you visit the Site or use the Service, The Behemoth may collect certain personal information. Personal information is information that is not otherwise publicly available, and may include such things as your first and last name, e-mail address, mailing address, and other information that you provide to us. If you choose to correspond with The Behemoth through e-mail, The Behemoth reserves the right to retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and The Behemoth's responses. Do not submit information that you do not want The Behemoth to access. As further described below, we may also collect non-personal information when you interact with the Site and Service such as information about your usage of the Site and Service. 

**_How The Behemoth Uses Your Information_**

The Behemoth may use personal information to provide information and services to you and to allow The Behemoth to (i) respond to questions and comments; (ii) analyze and monitor your use of the Site and the Service; (iii) promote, operate and support The Behemoth products and services, including to send you newsletters and periodic promotional materials; (iv) develop a knowledge base regarding its users; (v) process orders; (vi) improve the Site and Services; (vii) use for internal business purposes; (viii) inform appropriate authorities if deemed necessary; and (ix) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your personal information. 

**_How The Behemoth Discloses Your Information to Third Parties:_**

The Behemoth may disclose personal information as necessary to operate the Service, including in response to law enforcement activity, to enforce its contract or property rights, or when required by law. 

Information collected may also be transferred in connection with the sale or merger of the company (or substantially all of its assets) or any division or business line of the company to which the information relates or to any subsequent operator of the Site or Service. 

The Behemoth may hire third parties to perform services on its behalf in connection with operating the Site or Service in accordance with applicable law. 

If you direct any of your information, including personal information, to be shared with third parties, such as social media sites, third party mobile applications, and similar services, The Behemoth will have no control over these third party uses of your information. 

In addition to the disclosures set forth above, The Behemoth may aggregate or de-identify information about its users. Such aggregated or de-identified information may, in a manner that is not personally identifiable, be disclosed to third parties (including advertisers) for marketing, promotional, research, and other purposes. 

In those cases where de-identified data is shared with third parties, the third parties will not be able to identify any individual user of the Site or Service based on the disclosures. 

**_Passive information collection:_**

The Behemoth may use different technologies, such as cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts, and location-identifying technologies, to passively collect information. The information collected might include the date and time you visit the Site, logs from your browser or your use of the Service, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and the pages you requested. This information will usually be used to (i) customize the advertising and content you see, (ii) process and confirm your entries and order information, (iii) contact you, (iv) enhance your experience, and/or (v) improve our general user experience. Your browser must be set up to accept cookies in order to fully utilize certain areas of the Site. 

The Behemoth has the right to gather non-personal information regarding you, your game play activities, game usage, or preferences, THROUGH THE USE OF COOKIES OR OTHER MEANS, without any additional notice to you or affirmative actions taken by you BEYOND USING ANY OF THE SITE OR SERVICE. This non-personal information may include, but shall not be limited to, your IP address, age, gender, general location, The Behemoth game download history, Steam ID, PlayStation Network ID, Games for Windows LIVE ID, Xbox Live ID, game genre preferences, game achievements, game scores, game replays, technical specifications and other demographic information or statistics. Such information may be collected whether or not you register for an account with The Behemoth. Such information may also be collected while you are offline and may be transmitted to The Behemoth when you next connect to the Internet, regardless of the location where or device through which that connection is established. The Behemoth reserves the right to compile, save and use such information within the scope of The Behemoth's business activities, and analyze any and all of the data collected in this manner. The data collected by The Behemoth may be posted on websites accessible to the public; shared with console manufacturers, software developers, and/or marketing partners; or used by The Behemoth for any other lawful purpose. By using the Site and Service you consent to The Behemoth's use of the data The Behemoth collects, including the public display of information such as your user ID, your user created content or any other gameplay data. The Behemoth may also use such information for statistical purposes, the public display of user statistics and/or game rankings, to improve your game play experience, to provide you with advertisements or information that might be of interest to you, and any other reasonable purpose, at The Behemoth's sole discretion. 

**_Third Party Tracking and Do Not Track._**

There may be tracking technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Site and Service. Further, third parties may use tracking technologies in connection with our Site and Service, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services. We may not control those tracking technologies and we are not responsible for them. However, you understand that when you use our Service you may potentially encounter third party tracking technologies in connection with use of the Service and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the tracking technologies or practices of such third parties. For more information on our vendors, and their Tracking Technologies see the chart at the end of this policy. 

Your browser or other third party mechanisms may be able to allow you to signal or otherwise express your choice regarding the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (e.g., browser do not track signals). Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these 'do not track' signals or other mechanisms. 

**_How to Change your information and communications preferences:_**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. The Service may allow you to review, correct or update personal information you have provided through the Service's registration forms or otherwise, and you may provide registration updates and changes by contacting us here: 

Email: privacy[at]thebehemoth[dot]com 

If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable (but we may retain prior information as business records). You may cancel or modify our e-mail marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional e-mails or in some cases by logging into your Service account and changing your communication preferences, but we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Service, such as administrative and service announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications. 

**_Security:_**

The Behemoth intends to use commercially reasonable means to protect the integrity of its Site and Service, and the confidentiality of the personal information that you provide. While The Behemoth considers online privacy a priority, it cannot provide absolute assurances against, and will not be liable for, any breaches of confidentiality due to system failures or unauthorized access by third parties, and you use our Site and Service and provide us with your information at your own risk. 

**_Children & COPPA_**

We are a general audience service and do not use the Service to knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) that requires parental notice and consent under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ('COPPA') without such parental consent. In fact, if you are under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the Service and should not send any information about yourself to us through the Service. 

In the event that we become aware that we have collected personal information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with COPPA and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without COPPA-required consent, please contact us by email at: privacy[at]thebehemoth[dot]com 

**_International Users:_**

Our Service is operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Service or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing, controlling and storage of your information, including personal information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**_Your California Privacy Rights:_**

Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with The Behemoth or one of its subsidiaries may choose to opt out of The Behemoth's disclosure of personal information about them to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Unless noted at the time of collection, our policy is not to disclose personal information collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval, email privacy[at]thebehemoth[dot]com or write to The Behemoth at the address set forth below. 

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy:_**

The Behemoth reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. When material changes have been made to this Privacy Policy, The Behemoth will indicate this fact on the Site with a link to the revised version of the Privacy Policy and may provide notice to members of the revise Privacy Policy via email. Any material change to this Privacy Policy will also be indicated on the main page of the Site with a link to the revised Privacy Policy. Please check the Privacy Policy regularly to review the changes. 

**_Consent to this Privacy Policy:_**

By using the Site or the Service, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or the Service. Your continued use of the Site or the Service following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes. 

The Behemoth may disclose personal information as necessary to operate the Service, including in response to law enforcement activity, to enforce its contract or property rights, or when required by law. We do not sell, rent or lease your personal information. 

**_Contacting The Behemoth:_**

Questions regarding the Site or this Privacy Policy should be sent to: 

privacy[at]thebehemoth[dot]com
